Press Gang Publishers fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Published books, 1977 - 1999; F-184-9; 146 books (80 titles); Physical description: some titles exist in multiple editions, including translations into other languages. Each separate edition has been registered as a separate item. For most titles, Press Gang retained two copies.
  - Frank, K. Portland - The Anti-Psychiatry Bibliography and Resource Guide (second edition), July 1980; F-184-9-0-0-0-41 (Archival box - standard 184-54)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item72.
  - Frank, K. Portland - The Anti-Psychiatry Bibliography and Resource Guide (second edition, hardcopy), September 1979; F-184-9-0-0-0-42 (Archival box - standard 184-54)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item74.
  - Fuller, Janine and Stuart Blackley - Restricted Entry: Centsorship on Trial (second edition), June 1996; F-184-9-0-0-0-43 (Archival box - standard 184-54)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item76.
  - Hughes, Nym and Yvette Perreault, Yvonne Johnson - Stepping Out of Line: A Workbook on Lesbianism and Feminism, August 1984; F-184-9-0-0-0-44 (Archival box - standard 184-54)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item78.
  - Jacob, Suzanne - Life, After All, 1989; F-184-9-0-0-0-45 (Archival box - standard 184-54)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item79.
  - Jacob, Suzanne - la survie: nouvelles (deuxieme edition, Montreal: Le Biocreux inc), 1980; F-184-9-0-0-0-46 (Archival box - standard 184-55)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item80.
  - Jankola, Beth - Jody Said, 1977; F-184-9-0-0-0-47 (Archival box - standard 184-55)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item82.
  - Jones, Lizard - Two Ends of Sleep, 1997; F-184-9-0-0-0-48 (Archival box - standard 184-55)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item84.
  - Kiss and Tell - Drawing the Line: Lesbian Sexual Politics on the Wall (postcard book), April 1991; F-184-9-0-0-0-49 (Archival box - standard 184-55)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item85.
  - Lai, Larissa - When Fox is a Thousand (first edition), 1995; F-184-9-0-0-0-50 (Archival box - standard 184-55)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item87.
  - Lee, SKY - Bellydancer (first edition), 1994; F-184-9-0-0-0-51 (Archival box - standard 184-55)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item89.
  - Maracle, Lee - I Am Woman: A Native Perspective on Sociology and Feminism, 1996; F-184-9-0-0-0-52 (Archival box - standard 184-55)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item91.
  - Maracle, Lee - Ravensong: A Novel, May 1993; F-184-9-0-0-0-53 (Archival box - standard 184-55)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item93.
  - Maracle, Lee - Sojourner's Truth and Other Stories, December 1990; F-184-9-0-0-0-54 (Archival box - standard 184-55)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item95.
  - McLauglin, Karen - Choral, 1995; F-184-9-0-0-0-55 (Archival box - standard 184-55)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item96.
  - Mootoo, Shani - Cereus Blooms at Night, 1996; F-184-9-0-0-0-56 (Archival box - standard 184-56)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item98.
  - Mootoo, Shani - Cereus Blooms at Night (shortlisted for Chapters / Books in Canada First Novel Award), 1996; F-184-9-0-0-0-57 (Archival box - standard 184-56)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item100.
  - Mootoo, Shani - Cereus Blooms at Night (Toronto: McClelland and Stewart Inc.), 1998; F-184-9-0-0-0-58 (Archival box - standard 184-56)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item102.
  - Mootoo, Shani - Cereus Blooms at Night (advanced reader's edition, New York: Grove Press), 1998; F-184-9-0-0-0-59 (Archival box - standard 184-56)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item104.
  - Mootoo, Shani - Cereus Blooms at Night New York: Grove Press), 1998; F-184-9-0-0-0-60 (Archival box - standard 184-56)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item105.
  - Mootoo, Shani - De cereus bloeit 's nachts (Amsterdam: Utigeverij Contact), 1998; F-184-9-0-0-0-61 (Archival box - standard 184-56)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item108.
  - Mootoo, Shani - El Cereus Florece de Noche (Madrid: Editorial Debat), February 1999; F-184-9-0-0-0-62 (Archival box - standard 184-57)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item110.
  - Mootoo, Shani - Kaktusen blommar om natten (Tryckning: Albert Bonniers Förlag), 1999; F-184-9-0-0-0-63 (Archival box - standard 184-57)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item112.
  - Mootoo, Shani - Out On Main Street, 1993; F-184-9-0-0-0-64 (Archival box - standard 184-57)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item114.
  - Norgate, Sheila - Storm Clouds Over Party Shoes: Etiquette problems for the Ill-Bred Woman, 1997; F-184-9-0-0-0-65 (Archival box - standard 184-57)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item116.
  - Potrebenko, Helen - Sometimes they Sang, 1986; F-184-9-0-0-0-66 (Archival box - standard 184-57)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item118.
  - Richler, Nancy - Throwaway Angels (first edition), 1996; F-184-9-0-0-0-67 (Archival box - standard 184-57)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item120.
  - Shimrat, Irit - Call me Crazy: Stories from the Mad Movement, 1997; F-184-9-0-0-0-68 (Archival box - standard 184-57)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item122.
  - Silvera, Makeda - Her Head a Village, 1994; F-184-9-0-0-0-69 (Archival box - standard 184-57)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item124.
  - Taste This - Boys Like Her: Transfictions, 1998; F-184-9-0-0-0-70 (Archival box - standard 184-57)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item125.
  - Telling it Book Collective - Telling It: Women and Language Across Cultures, October 1990; F-184-9-0-0-0-71 (Archival box - standard 184-57)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item127.
  - Tulchinsky, Karen X. - Love Ruins Everything, 1998; F-184-9-0-0-0-72 (Archival box - standard 184-58)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item129.
  - Van de Walle, Elly - Falling From Grace, February 1984; F-184-9-0-0-0-73 (Archival box - standard 184-58)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item131.
  - Warland, Betsy - InVersions: Writing by Dykes, Queers and Lesbians, September 1991; F-184-9-0-0-0-74 (Archival box - standard 184-58)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item133.
  - Warland, Betsy - Proper Deafinitions: Collected Theorgrams, May 1990; F-184-9-0-0-0-75 (Archival box - standard 184-58)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item135.
  - Williams, Jana - Scuttlebutt, July 1990; F-184-9-0-0-0-76 (Archival box - standard 184-58)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item137.
  - Williams, Jana - Scuttlebutt (New York: Firebrand Books), 1990; F-184-9-0-0-0-77 (Archival box - standard 184-58)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item139.
  - Women's Research Centre - Recollecting Our Lives: Women's Experience of Childhood Sexual Abuse, November 1989; F-184-9-0-0-0-78 (Archival box - standard 184-58)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item141.
  - Wong, Rita - Monkeypuzzle, 1998; F-184-9-0-0-0-79 (Archival box - standard 184-58)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item143.
  - Kiss and Tell - Her Tongue on My Theory, 1994; F-184-9-0-0-0-80 (Archival box - standard 184-58)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item145.